Speaker: Most shops sell online,
and a lot of people go to the website rather than the actual shop.
Since the Covid-19 pandemic, shopping online is even more popular.
The first time you use a website, you can create an account
where you give your personal details and choose a password for next time you shop.
Or if you don’t want to do this, you can usually shop as a guest.
You choose what you want to buy
and click on the item to add it to your basket.
When you are ready to pay, you click on
‘continue to checkout’.
You give the delivery address where you want them to send your things.
You usually pay extra for next-day delivery –
standard delivery is sometimes free.
Then you review your order to check it is correct.
You choose how you want to pay, for example,
with a bank card, and give your card details,
that is, the number and expiry date.
Finally, you place your order
and receive a reference number and a confirmation email.
And then you wait.